

**Auckland Central** 022 429 3615 phoebesu85@yahoo.com.tw linkedin.com/in/phoebe-su github.com/phoebesu1025 Visa status:Permanent residence

# Summary

A knack for problem-solving and a positive, creative mindset. I gain immense satisfaction from crafting solutions and seeing tangible impacts for people. Committed to producing highquality work that makes a difference.

Currently an assistant trainer at Mission Ready, where I support aspiring developers to grow their skills.

Prior, 3 years as a professional chef before retraining into tech.

# **Skills**

#### **Frontend**

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Ionic TypeScript
- Material UITailwind

#### Backend

- Node.is
- Restful API

### **Database**

- MySql
- MongoDB

#### AI Tool

- Google Dialogflow
- Azure Bing

# Phoebe Su - Junior Developer

# **Work Experience**

# Auckland Council - The Southern Initiative | Feb 2023 - Apr 2023 **Software Developer Intern**

Collaborated with two other interns, a developer and a UX designer, to develop a cross-platform mobile app aimed at closing the employment gap for Māori and Pacifika students in Auckland.

#### **Achievement:**

- Successfully executed the development of new features for the student dashboard within a stringent 10 week time
- Improved the quality of the JavaScript codebase (Typescript)
- Close collaborated with the team (Agile) to create an great user experience

# Technologies & Tools used:

React, Ionic Framework, TypeScript, CSS, GitHub

### Mission Ready HQ

l Jan 2023 - Current

## **Full Stack Development Assistant Trainer**

Before I finished my level 5 study, I was hand-picked to take an assistant trainer role, guiding Level 4 student using my knowledge and previous experiences

The trainer presents the content then I an one other Assistant Trainer provide all other support, mentoring and extra sessions for 25 students.

- Prepare contents and exercises as needed
- Hold study groups and afternoon sessions to answer auestions.
- Document and identify risk students and reporting to retention team
- Represented Mission Ready at Sisters In Tech Expo 2023 and STEM Expo talking with school/Uni students about our courses

### **Achievement:**

Received positive feedback from students and trainers, and asked to renew the contract for this role.

# **Technologies & Tools used:**

React, JavaScript, CSS, GitHub, Node.js, MySQL, Material UI

## **Other Experience**

| Jul 2019 - Aug 2022

#### **Proessional chef**

Throughout my career, I have consistently demonstrated the ability to learn quickly and work in a reliable and organized manner. As a result, I have been able to achieve rapid promotion within my previous roles.

### **Achievement:**

 Offered a part-time then full-time role as a chef at QT Hotel, an hotel chain that was hard to get into as a junior chef in the hotel opening team.

### **Transferable Skills to Tech:**

 High level of discipline and attention to detail, strong need for team work, ability to think creatively and deliver under pressure.

Pavilion Cafe, Auckland | Jun 2021 - Aug 2022
Chef de Partie / Senior Chef (Full-time)
QT Hotel, Auckland | Oct 2020 - Jun 2021
Commis Chef/ Larder Chef (Full-time)
QT Hotel, Wellington | Jul 2019 - Dec 2019
Commis Chef (Part-time)

# **Education**

# Mission Ready HQ

| Aug 2022 - Apr 2023

# **NZQA Level 6 Applied Technology Product Solutions (Software)**

- A practical, mentored, real-world work experience.
- Interned with Auckland Council see above for details.

### NZQA Level 5 Cloud and DevOps Developer Accelerator

- Intensive course in solving complex enterprise-level problems using Cloud, Artificial Intelligence, and DevOps practices.
- Cloud service (Azure, Bing Search, azure deploy), AI (Chat-bot with google dialog flow), DevOps and automated deployment (CI/CD), No-SQL database (MongoDB), Restful API, Unit testing.

#### NZQA Level 4 Full Stack Developer Accelerator

• Developed foundational skills in coding, including building responsive full stack web apps, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, and MySQL.

#### Le Cordon Bleu New Zealand

| Feb 2017 - Dec 2019

#### **Bachelor of Culinary Arts and Business**

- Completed a conjoint degree in business and culinary arts.
- Chosen as one of the two students who would represent Le Cordon Bleu in the Wellington City Council international student welcome 2019. Spoke with future students about our courses and experiences.

# Reference

# 1. Sebin Benjamin

Technical Trainer And Mentor at Mission Ready HQ <a href="mailto:Sebin@missionreadyhq.com">Sebin@missionreadyhq.com</a>

#### 2. Atarau Pouwhare-Ellis

Kaihautū at TSI Auckland Council <u>Atarau.pouwhare-</u> ellis@aucklandcouncil.govt.nz

More referees are available upon request